## Davi Silva Alves de Oliveira

#### davi.comp.oliveira@gmail.com

Phone: (88) 99766-0734 Fortaleza - CE, Brazil

## **Profile**

Working as a **fullstack development intern** at Elevar Commerce.

I am an undergraduate student in Information Systems at the Federal University of Ceará - Quixadá Campus and a web developer with experience in React, Angular, Node, and other development technologies.

My experiences are primarily focused on frontend, but I also work on backend projects using Node and Java.

Check out my projects on **GitHub** or connect with me on **LinkedIn**.

## Professional Experience

Dec 2022 - Present | Fullstack Development Intern at Elevar Commerce

• Develop and maintain web applications for an Ecommerce, both frontend and backend, as well as integrations and other functionalities inherent to this type of product;

Skills: Angular · Angular<br/>JS · Angular Universal · Vue · Nuxt · Node · Java · Firebase · SCSS (Sass) · SQL · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

Jul 2021 - Nov 2022 | Frontend Development Scholar at GREat - Computer Networks, Software Engineering, and Systems Group at UFC by FUNCAP

• Develop and maintain web applications focused on order and process management for the Government of the State of Ceará;

Skills: React · HTML · SCSS (Sass) · Ant Design · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

## **Projects and Technologies**

Click on the name of each project to access the respective GitHub repository.

- HTML and CSS:
  - Star Wars Dashboard | 2021
    - \* Sample web application displaying information about the Star Wars franchise.
- React:
  - User Management Site | 2022
    - \* Simple project for a user management interface.
  - Click Project Site | 2022
    - \* Project for voting on movies for display in a school or institution.
  - Country Quiz | 2022
    - \* Country quiz with dynamic questions generated from an API with information about countries, cities, etc.
  - Tic-Tac-Toe Game | 2022
    - \* Simple tic-tac-toe game to play with up to 2 players.
  - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022
    - \* Web page for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental company in Quixadá.
- Angular:
  - MFE with Module Federation | 2023
    - \* Testing the concept of Micro Frontends with Angular applications.
  - Trakto TV | 2023

- \* Application made using the Trakto API.
- Dynamic Layout | 2023
  - \* Application testing the concept of dynamic layout with Angular.
- Vue:
  - Poké Search | 2023
    - \* Application for listing and searching for Pokémon using the Poké API.
  - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022
    - \* Web page for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental company in Quixadá.
- Node:
  - Click Project API | 2022
    - \* Backend for the Click Project, a project for voting on movies for display in a school or institution.
  - Vehicle Rental System API | 2022
    - \* Backend for the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental company in Quixadá.
- Java:
  - User Management API | 2022
    - \* Backend for the user management interface project.
- Kotlin:
  - Vehicle Rental System App | 2023
    - \* Native Android app for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental company in Quixadá.

#### Skills

- Angular;
- Angular Universal;
- Vue:
- React;
- Node:
- Java;
- Typescript;
- Scss (Sass);
- Scrum;
- Git;
- PostgreSQL;
- Prisma.

## Education

## 2022 - Present | Bachelor's in Information Systems - UFC Quixadá Campus - CE, Brazil

• Bachelor's degree in Information Systems with a focus on information system and web development.

### 2020 - 2022 | Bachelor's in Computer Engineering - UFC Quixadá Campus - CE, Brazil (Interrupted)

• Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering with a focus on embedded systems development with C and Assembly. Interrupted for change of course.

## 2017 - 2019 | Computer Networks Technician - IFCE Tauá Campus - CE, Brazil

 Technical formation in Computer Networks with a focus on network administration, structured cabling, and computer maintenance.

#### Languages

- English Advanced
- Spanish Beginner
- Portuguese (Brazilian) Native

# Portfolio and Contact (click to access)

- GitHub
- LinkedIn
- Lattes Curriculum

This resume was entirely made in Markdown based on the example available at CV Example.